（壁(へき)）ハッ…
（貂(てん)）隊長ーっ！
Captain!
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）古代中国
Ancient China.
聖者の時代は終わりを告げ
人間の欲望は解放されていた
After learning that the era of saints had ended,
human desire was unleashed.
戦乱の嵐が
500年にわたって吹き荒れ
And a storm of violent wars erupted for 500 years...
100を超えた国々は
７つに淘汰(とうた)された
until over one hundred states were reduced to merely seven.
そして今 西の果ての国 秦(しん)から―
And now, a wind of great history gusts from the State of Qin in the far West.
大いなる歴史が
生まれようとしている
This is the tumultuous tale of a nameless boy and a young king who brought the warring era to its end!
これは
戦乱の時代を生き抜いた―
名もなき少年と若き王の
激動の物語である
（信(しん)）ンンッ！
Presented by Anime-Destiny
Translation
kewl0210
itsumo yori hayaku kietetta hoshi zora ni
いつもより早く消えてった星空に
In a starry sky that disappeared faster than it ever has
kusanariatta deai wa
重なり合った出会いは
the many piled up meetings we've had
Editing
jagman1x3
ore wo nomikonde iku
俺を呑み込んでいく
swallow me.
kono yume wa kudakenai
この夢は砕けない
This dream cannot be broken.
Timing
rtrs
sabitsukaseta kyoufushin
錆びつかせた恐怖心
Among this rusted fear in my heart
yuragu fuan no naka de
揺らぐ不安の中で
and the anxiety that makes me waver
Typesetting
rtrs
ame wo saegiru shinjitsu
雨を遮る信実
is a truth that interrupts the rain.
Karaoke
kewl0210
FZeroWing
dare ni mo ubaeyashinai
誰にも奪えやしない
No one can take it away,
onaji keshiki ni hisonda puraido
同じ景色にひそんだプライド
our pride that lurks in the same landscape.
Encode
max80
itsuka kitto kanau ima mo mieru kibou fortitude
いつかきっと叶う 今も見える希望 fortitude
The fortuitous desire I have will definitely come true one day.
yowasa wo sute wa shinai
弱さを捨てはしない
We won't throw away our weaknesses,
oretachi no kienai shiin
俺達の消えないシーン
those are scenes that won't disappear.
furenzokusen no youni hashiru kibou unbreakable heart
不連続線の様に走る希望 unbreakable heart
My desire in my unbreakable heart runs like a discontinuitous line.
I knew at the start that there's no end.
QC
Mistral[sA]
I've made up my mind, right now it's the time to take the first step.
Distro
kokus
Kittie
prefix-
Qpax
Now's the only time.
～♪
The Power of the Sword
Xin... Xin!
（漂(ひょう)）信…
信…
ハッ！ 漂？
（漂）ハハッ… 気がついたか？
Piao?!
Finally awake?
Huh?
あれ？ あっ 俺 頭打たれて…
Ah... My head got hit...
Now we're tied again.
これで また五分だ
（信）くそ～！
Dammit!
うん？ 見ろ 信
（信）うん？
Look, Xin.
（漂）死体だ
It's a corpse.
朱凶(しゅきょう)…
思い出した！ 俺がやったんだ
Zhuxiong. I remember!
I beat him.
とどめを刺したのは別のヤツだけど
どのみち 俺の傷で死んでいた
Well, another guy gave the finishing blow,
but he would've died by the wounds I gave him anyhow.
お前の敵(かたき)を取ったんだ
I avenged you!
でも まだだぜ
これから本当の敵を…
But just you wait.
I'm about to get real revenge...
敵は 朱凶で十分だよ
（信）えっ？
Zhuxiong was plenty enough for revenge.
これから先は そうじゃないはずだ
What comes next is a different matter, Xin!
信！
（信）ハッ…
漂 どこ行くんだ？
Piao, where're you going?!
漂 待ってくれ！
Piao, wait!
Piao?
（政(せい)）漂？
（信）うん？
Zheng!
政…
（政）どうした？ 信
What's wrong, Xin?
いつまで寝ている気だ？
How long are you intending to sleep?
（信）…るせえ　こっちは
体中 ボロボロで動けねえんだよ
Sheddep. My body's so beat up I can't move!
“天下の大将軍”が聞いてあきれる
I'm astonished to hear that from the greatest general under the heavens.
な… なんだと てめえ！
ぶっ飛ばすぞ！
Wh-What was that, bastard?!
I'll beat the shit outta you!
悔しかったら さっさと起きろ
If you feel frustrated, then hurry and wake up.
I told you... Even if I want to, right now my body won't...
ンンッ…
だから 今は動きたくても体が…
Xin.
信…
なっ… バカな
I don't believe it...
Even though he'd lost the will to fight, with one word from Chengjiao...
戦意を喪失していたのに
成蟜(せいきょう)の言葉ひとつで…
A rare species of ape unlike any you've ever seen...
（成蟜）
“見たこともない珍種の猿の赤子”
That's what the black market merchant that sold me Lankai said.
（成蟜）そう言って
闇の商人はランカイを売っていった
At first, I just took care of him out of curiosity, but what do you think now?
最初は 興味本位で飼ってみたが…
どうだ？
僅か数年で
こんな化け物に成長しおった
In just a few years he grew into this monster.
Because I scrupulously trained him since he was a child,
赤子のときから
念入りに調教したおかげで―
he'll listen to anything I say.
こいつは俺の言うことを何でも聞く
何でもだ！ アハハハッ！
Anything!
クッ… 何だ？
What?
何なんだ？ さっきから お前は！
（成蟜）うん？
What the hell is with you?!
I saw lots of different kinds of people in Heibei Village,
黒卑村(こくひむら)で
いろんなヤツを見てきたけど
お前ほどの
ゲス野郎は いなかった！
but there wasn't anybody as much of a lowlife bastard as you!
フフフッ… ゴミ虫が鳴いておるわ
It seems the insects are chirping.
おい 虫けら
それ以上 くさい息を吐くな
Hey, insect, don't exhale out any more smelly breath. You're dirtying the royal palace.
王宮が汚(けが)れる
貴様ら民衆は
愚かで利己的で 欺き 殺し 奪う
You people foolishly and selfishly deceive, kill, and steal.
他人を出し抜くことに
没頭する卑しい生き物だ
You're vulgar creatures that immerse yourself in the idea of taking advantage of others.
王国とは 支配する側と
される側とで成り立っている
A kingdom is made up of the side that rules and the side that are ruled.
貴様らが より低く
我らが より高くあるときこそ―
The moment I am higher and you all are lower
is the moment the country gains wealth and stability.
国は富み 安定を得る
貴様らは
ただ我らに ひれ伏せばよい
All you need to do is prostrate yourselves before me.
That is the true form of the controlled side!
それが 支配される側のあるべき姿
我らの務めは 王家の血を盤石にし
Our duty is to fortify the royal bloodline,
更なる高みに上り
強固な国を築くこと
climb to further heights, and build a stable country...
だが 政は より純血な
王族である俺を差し置いて―
But Zheng disregarded me, who has purer royal blood, and took the throne.
玉座に就いた
だから排除されたのだ
That's why he was removed!
The royal family must be inherited by one who is worthy of carrying the royal family!
（成蟜）王族は
王族に ふさわしき者によって―
継承されねばならぬ
That's the problem with countries!
これは 国家の問題だ！
何か反論があるか？ 愚民のガキ
（貂）ウッ…
Is there anything you'd like to say back?!
Brat of the ignorant masses?!
What the hell is... "the problem with countries"?
（信）なにが“国家の問題”だ…
（成蟜）うん？
（貂）信！
（信）ンンッ…
Xin!
なんだ 貴様
まだ生きておったのか
What...?
You're still alive, bastard?
ピンピンしてらぁ…
Alive and kicking.
Chengjiao...
成蟜…
お前は 呂不韋(りょふい)の留守を突き
政を襲って 玉座を奪った
You took advantage of Lü Buwei being away, attacked Zheng, and stole the throne.
“欺き 殺し 奪う”
"Deceive, kill, steal"?
お前が さっき言った
愚民そのものじゃねえか
You're just like one of the ignorant people you just described!
I'm amazed to hear that from a pure blooded member of the royal family!
“純血な王族”が聞いてあきれるぜ
血が どうのこうの言っても
本当のところは―
No matter what you say about your blood,
you just had a lot of unjustified anger at Zheng for taking the throne, didn't you?!
政に王位を持っていかれて
逆恨みしただけだろう！
愚民が何を聞いていた？
政を排除したのは国の正しい在り方
What do think you're asking, you ignorant commoner?!
Removing Zheng was the right thing to do for the country...
小難しいことを言われても
分かんねえんだよ！
I'm not gonna understand the complicated details!
The thing I understand perfectly is...
はっきり分かってることはよ
どんなに お前が偉ぶってても
身を張って―
that no matter how high and mighty you act,
there's not one person who'll put themselves on the line to protect you!
お前を守ろうとするヤツは
１人もいねえってことだ！
（どよめき）
（役人）なんということを…
（信）結局 お前に従うのは
何にも知らねえ猿１匹だ
When it comes down to it, the only thing that obeys you is an ape that doesn't know any better!
気色悪いんだよ てめえら！
You people are disgusting!
（竭氏(けつし)）
負け犬の遠ぼえですぞ 成蟜さま！
Those are just the cries of a loser, Lord Chengjiao!
フン…
Hey, someone. Bring him to me.
おい 誰か そいつらを連れてこい
王自ら 首を落としてやる
The king wishes to personally take his head.
（役人）なっ！ し… しかし
ヤツは剣を持っております
B-But he has a sword!
You guys are remarkably good at escaping death anyhow!
（成蟜）
どうせ 死に損ないではないか
それとも 貴様ら 全員
ランカイの餌食になりたいのか？
Or would you rather all be food for Lankai?!
This is Lord Chengjiao's command.
成蟜さまの仰せである
今すぐ その者どもを捕らえよ！
Capture that boy at once!
Okay, let's go.
My eyes!
目がー！
（役人）アアッ… どうした？
H-Hey, what happened?!
Are you all right?!
Now then, ain't it about time you got down from there, Chengjiao?
さあ そろそろ そこをどけよ 成蟜
政が 外で怒ってっぞ！
Zheng is pretty mad outside!
（兵士２）ヤッ！
（兵士１）グッ… まだまだ！
Not yet!
（刺す音）
ウワッ！
Your highness, forgive me...
大王 お許しを…
Totch, Fuuji.
（楊端和(ようたんわ)）
トッヂ フウヂ 秦王を守れ
Protect the Qin King.
万が一があってはならん
（トッヂ･フウヂ）はっ！
Do not allow any possibility for the worst!
M'am!
Ramauji, watch their backs.
ラマウジ 後ろを任す
（ラマウジ）はっ！
M'am!
（魏興(ぎこう)）フン…
（昌文君(しょうぶんくん)）
やはり 地上からでは分が悪いか…
As I thought, him having the high ground puts me at a disadvantage.
Changwenjun!
昌文君！ ウオーッ！
If I keep blocking Weixing, I'll lose.
魏興を防ぎ続けても
こちらは負ける
大王の檄(げき)で上がった士気も
この人数差では そろそろ限界だ
Against such numbers, the morale boost the king gave us will soon reach its limit!
時間がない… 急げ 信！
We're running out of time! Hurry, Xin!
Watch out!
危ねえ！
ウワ～ッ！
ジャマだ　向こうへ行ってろ！
You're in the way! Get over there!
“向こう”って どこだよ！
化け猿 暴れ回り過ぎなんだよ
Where is "over there"?!
That ape monster's rampaging all over the place!
チッ… やっぱムリか
どうなってんだ？ こいつの体は
Dang, it's really not working.
What the hell is with his body?!
（蹴る音）
ウワッ！
グアッ…
だ… 大丈夫か？ 信
（信）アアッ…
Are you okay, Xin?!
ああ あばらを少し やられただけだ
いてて…
He just got a couple ribs.
Lankai, finish them!
ランカイ とどめを刺せ
（信）
く… くそ… どうすりゃいいんだ？
D-Dammit... What do I do...?
That ape's almost dead...
あの猿は もうひと息なのに…
But my sword... Is my sword no good?
剣じゃ… 剣じゃダメなのか！
（壁）そんなことはない！
That's not so!
Have more faith in your sword!
もっと剣を信じるんだ
けど あいつに
剣は効かなかったじゃねえかよ！
But the sword hasn't been working on him!
それは
まだ お前の腕が未熟なだけだ
That's just because your skill is still immature!
なに！
What?!
The sword has been honed by 500 years of Chinese history, it's the strongest of all weapons!
（壁）剣とは 中華500年の
騒乱が育んだ最強の武器だ
Among all the weapons that exist,
数ある武器の中で 剣は―
the sword has done nothing but evolve for the goal of defeating enemies.
ただひたすら敵を倒すことだけを
追求し 進化してきた
Everything depends on the person using it!
全ては使い手しだい
それが 剣という武器の本質だ
That is the essence of the weapon known as a sword!
お前には それが分かるはずだ！
You should know that!
（信）使い手しだい…
It depends on the person using it...
“線”と“点”
Lines and... a point.
I see.
なるほど　悪くねえ
（貂）おい
Not bad!
Hey, are you gonna go at him with the sword again?
また剣でやるのか？
Diao, tie my right hand with the ribbon from the scabbard!
貂 鞘(さや)のヒモで
俺の右手を縛ってくれ
By the way, Diao,
ところで 貂 お前
when this is over, how much do you think you're gonna rake in from Zheng?
これが終わったら 一体
いくら 政から ぶんどる気だ？
えっ？ いくらとかまでは
まだ考えてないよ
I haven't thought about how much or anything yet.
何だよ？ こんなときに
Why bring it up at a time like this?
なんだ そうか
んじゃ そろそろ考えておけ
Oh, is that right?
Well, you'd better start thinking about it!
（貂）えっ？
（信）隊長！
Captain! Could you find some way to stop that big ape from moving?!
なんとか
その大猿の動きを止めてくれ
10… いや ５つ数えるだけでいい
そうすりゃ 俺が しとめる
Until you can count to 10... No, just 5 is fine!
If you can do that, I can take him down!
（バジオウ）いいだろう
All right, then.
シュンメン！
（シュンメン）んっ…
Shunmen!
つぶせ ランカイ！
Crush them, Lankai!
Run!
逃げろ！
（信）タジフ！
Tajif!
これで どうだ？ 少年！
How's this, boy?!
十分だ！
That's plenty!
あっ…
（信）力じゃねえ
It's not about strength...
剣と一身になり
I need to become one with the sword
一分のブレもなく
and without one bit of deviation
ただ まっすぐに…
make it point straight down
to make this one point
この一点だけを！
グアーッ！
pierce!
突き通す！
あっ… ウワッ！
戦う気のねえヤツは寝てろ
Anybody who doesn't feel like fighting should go to bed!
どうした？ ランカイ　立て！
What're you doing, Lankai?!
Stand up!
Why don't you get up, you ape monster?!
立たんか 化け猿！
立って その虫けらどもをつぶせ！
さもなくば お仕置きだぞ！
Stand up and crush those insects!
If you don't, I'll punish you!
（信）今更 脅しが効くもんか
Threats ain't gonna work now.
そいつは もう立てねえよ
He can't stand up anymore.
It's over, Chengjiao!
終わりだ 成蟜
How...?
（竭氏）なぜだ？
なぜ こうなった？
How did this happen...?
嬴政(えいせい) 昌文君 王騎(おうき)
Ying Zheng, Changwenjun, Wang Qi...
Yang Duan He, Mountain People, and that riffraff brat.
楊端和 山の民
愚民のガキ…
What is the cause for their victory?
ヤツらの勝因は何だ？
Everything... If they were missing any one element, this would not have happened.
全てだ　どれか ひとつでも
欠けていれば こうは ならなかった
Did they walk a tightrope to reach this point, as well...?
ヤツらも 綱渡りで
ここまで来たということか
悔しい…
It was mortifying...
あの成蟜ごときクソガキにまで
ひざまずき…
Having to kneel to a shitty brat like that Chengjiao...
And the work of exhausting every means to rise to the position of chancellor...
いや あらゆる手を尽くして
丞相(じょうしょう)にまで上り詰めた苦労が…
呂不韋を殺し
秦国を独占する夢が…
My dream of killing Lü Buwei and ruling over the State of Qin...
全て消える… 全てが…
has all vanished... All of it...
（役人たち）ヒイーッ！
き… 貴様ら！
逃げるな　戦わんか！
Y-You bastards!
Don't run! You need to fight!
死罪！ 全員 死罪に処すぞ！
Death! You will all be punished with death!
（役人Ａ）何をしてる！ 早くしろ
（役人Ｂ）押すな！ 扉が引けぬ
What are you doing, hurry!
Don't push! We can't pull the door open!
（役人Ｃ）いや 開かぬ！
（役人Ａ）もう おしまいだ…
No, it won't open!
It's all over!
Over...?
（竭氏）おしまいだと？
いや 終わってはおらぬ
No! It has not ended!
わ… わしは
まだ終わってはおらぬ！
I-I'm still not done!
どけい！
Out of the way!
（役人）丞相！ 割り込みは…
Chancellor! Pushing your way through won't...
（竭氏）やかましい！
わしは まだ終わっておらぬ！
Shut your mouth!
I'm not done yet!
城外に出れば
８万の軍が待機しておる
If we can escape the castle, there are 80,000 soldiers on standby!
開けろ！ この扉を開けろ！
（信）哀れなヤツだな お前は
Open it! Open this door!
You sure are pathetic, ain'cha?
クッ… 貴様ら まさか この俺を…
You bastards, you don't intend to...
愚民のぶんざいで 王族である俺を
斬ろうとでもいうのか！
Do you ignorant commoners actually intend to kill me, a member of the royal family?!
What else would we be doing?
それ以外ねえだろう
ふざけるな！ バカか？ 貴様は
Don't screw around! Are you an idiot?!
そんなことが
許されるとでも思っているのか！
Do you honestly think something like that can be forgiven?!
我は秦国の王であるぞ！
そんなこと…
I am the king of the State of Qin!
Such a thing cannot happen!
ありえぬわー！
あるんだよ　戦争だからな
Yeah it can.
Because this is war.
（騰(とう)）残念ながら
ここを通すわけには まいりませぬ
Unfortunately, I cannot let you through here.
By the orders of my lord, I will be cutting down anyone who approaches this door.
我が殿の命により 扉に近づく者は
斬り捨てさせていただきます
（竭氏）グウッ…
な… なぜ王騎の副官が？
いや それより…
Wh-Why is Wang Qi's lieutenant...?
No, more importantly...
竭氏を逃がすな！
Don't let Jie Shi get away!
戦を終わらせるには
ヤツの首が必要だ！
We need his head to end the war!
Understood.
（バジオウ）分かった
死んでたまるか
Me, die?!
死んでたまるか…
Oh no!
いかん…
その扉の向こうは迷路になってる
It turns into a maze past that door!
入られたら 確実に見失うぞ
If he gets in, we'll definitely lose track of him!
どけ 虫けら！ 踏みつぶすぞ！
Out of the way, insect!
I'll crush you under my foot!
外すなよ 貂
Don't miss, Diao!
Like I could miss this!
外すかよ！
（吹き矢の音）
ウワーッ！
D-Don't fuck with me!
ふざけるな！
わしは 大秦国…
I am a leader of the Great State of Qin,
Chancellor Jie!
竭丞相ぞー！
（斬る音）
ウワッ！
We did it. We finally did it!
やった… ついに やったぞ
あの呂氏ですら
暗殺できなかった竭氏を討った
Jie Shi, the man even Lü Buwei couldn't assassinate, has been killed!
で… 出口
Th-The exit...
死んでたまるか…
There's no way... I'll die...
ハッ！
（壁）て… 貂！
D-Diao!
て… てめえ！
Y-You bastard!
Xin! He's running! Follow him!
信 ヤツが逃げるぞ！ 追うんだ！
ヒッ… ヒイッ！
Go after Chengjiao, Xin!
成蟜を追うんだ 信！
（信）ヤツの行き場は もうねえ
He's got nowhere left to run.
He has a pulse.
脈はある
Hey, Diao.
おい 貂 もう少しで
念願の大金が手に入るんだぞ
Just a little further and you'll get all the money you want.
あんな ひでえ村での生活とは
大違いのすげえ暮らしが待ってんだ
A great life, totally different from the one you lived in that awful village, is waiting for you...
こんなんで くたばんじゃねえぞ
You can't drop dead in a place like this!
壁のあんちゃん 貂を頼むぜ
Brother Bi!
Take care of Diao!
Right.
間違いだ
A mistake...
これは何かの間違いだ
俺は 秦国の王 成蟜
This must be some mistake...
I'm the king of the State of Qin, Chengjiao!
I'm the king... I'm the king...
俺が王… 俺が王…
I'm the king!
俺が王だー！
（壁）すまない 貂…
I'm sorry, Diao.
I'm sorry this had to happen to you...
お前をこんな目に遭わせてしまって
貂 死なないでくれ…
Diao... Please don't die!
くそ… ともかく止血だ
Shit! Anyway, I need to stop the bleeding!
Maybe I can still make it!
まだ間に合うかもしれない ハッ…
鎖帷子(くさりかたびら)…
Chainmail...
ハハハハッ…
かなわないよ 君たちには
I'm no match for you guys.
You really are some incredible boys.
本当に すごい少年たちだ
大丈夫だよ タジフ　傷は深くない
（貂）ウウッ…
It's okay, Tajif.
The wound isn't deep.
貂 今すぐ止血してやるからな
Diao, I'll stop the bleeding right now, okay?
Diao, you're...
貂 君は…
（肆氏(しし)）うん？ 成蟜さま！
Lord Chengjiao!
なぜ こんな所に お１人で？
What are you doing out here alone?!
一体…
What on earth...
Did something happen in the inner palace?!
まさか 本殿で何か…
Please tell me. Why did you come here alone?
お答えください
なぜ お１人で まいられたのですか
丞相や ほかの大臣たちは
どうなされました？
What happened to the chancellor and the other ministers?!
Jie Shi was... killed.
丞相は… 殺された
What?!
なに？
What is it you said, my lord?!
何を申されます？
丞相が殺されたなど ありえませぬ
There's simply no way the chancellor could have been killed!
一体 誰が殺したというのです？
一体 誰が…
Just who is it you say killed him?
Who could have?!
回廊から入ってきた猿どもだ！
The monkeys that came in from the corridor!
左慈(さじ)が抜かれたというのか？
まさか… ありえぬ！
They got past Zuoci?!
No... it can't be!
Lord Chengjiao, I'll ask once again.
成蟜さま もう一度 伺います
竭丞相は命を落とされたのですね？
Has Chancellor Jie lost his life?!
万が一にも生きているという…
If there's any chance he's still alive...
首だけになって
生きられる人間がいるか！
Do you think there's a human that can live as a head?!
Chancellor Jie has died...
竭丞相が死んだ…
Doesn't that mean we've lost?!
それでは 我らの負けではないか…
肆氏！ 貴様 丞相の参謀であろうが
なんとかせぬか！
Shi Shi! You're the chancellor's officer, aren't you?!
Can't you do something?!
おやめください 成蟜さま…
Please stop, Lord Chengjiao.
Chengjiao?!
（昌文君）成蟜…
Why is he here...?!
なぜ こんな所に…
ハッ！ まさか…
Could it be?!
王騎将軍…
General Wang Qi...
General Wang Qi!
（兵士）王騎将軍！
（兵士）王騎将軍だと？
Did you say General Wang Qi!?
General Wang Qi!
王騎将軍 いつの間に王宮に…
いや 何をしに ここに…
When did he come into the palace...?
No, why's he coming here?!
（魏興）王騎将軍！
（肆氏）うん？
General Wang Qi!
（魏興）
貴殿に ひとつ聞きたいことがある
I have something I wish to ask you!
なぜ偽りの首を差し出した？
Why did you present us with a fake head?!
納得のいく答えがあろうや？
なければ ここで死んでもらう
Do you have any satisfactory answer?
If not, you'll die where you stand.
昌文君のニセ首を差し出した王騎が
我らの敵であることは もはや明白
Wang Qi, having falsely presented Changwenjun's head,
is already clearly our enemy.
魏興 さすがは我が右腕
Weixing, just what I'd expect from my right hand.
王騎軍との戦いになるならば
勝機は 王騎の首を取る以外にない
If this turns into a fight with the Wang Qi army,
we cannot have victory without taking Wang Qi's head.
今なら 馬上 対 地上
魏興が負けることは万が一にもない
Right now he's mounted on a horse and has the higher ground.
There isn't a sliver of a chance that Weixing could lose!
相手が将軍とて 容赦は要らん
There's no need for mercy, even if your opponent is a general!
Kill him!
やれ！
Th... This is...
（肆氏）こ… これが…
王騎か！
Wang Qi?!
降りそうで降らない この曇天
I wonder if rain will fall from these clouds or not...
嫌いじゃありませんねえ
I really wouldn't mind it.
何をしに来た？ 王騎
Why did you come here, Wang Qi?!
Might you be betraying Chengjiao and joining our side?!
もしや 成蟜を裏切り
我らにつくということか？
ンフフフッ… ご冗談を
Quite the jest.
あまりに かわいらしい
じゃれ合いが続いていたので―
Your sweet little squabble was dragging on a little much,
so I thought I'd dirty the field up a bit.
少々 場を濁しに来ただけですよ
What did you say, you bastard?!
なんだと？ 貴様
どこまで愚弄する気だ？
Just how much do you intend to mock us?!
（政）将軍よ
General.
用件があるなら早く言え
俺たちは忙しい
If you have business with us, hurry and say it.
We are busy.
今 お前に かまっている暇はない
We do not have time to spend on you right now!
ンフッ…
あなたの命をいただきに来ました
I came to take your life.
kowaresou na kokoro tsumugu youni
壊れそうな心 紡ぐように
To weave together my breaking heart
yume no kakera mitsume (No more cry)
夢のカケラ見つめ (No more cry）
I gaze at the fragments of a dream (No more crying)
me no mae ni wa tsuki ga utsushidasu
目の前には月が映し出す
The moon I see before my eyes
kono mune no yakusoku
この胸の約束
reflects this promise in my heart
namida ga nokoshita kioku sae mo
涙が残した記憶さえも
I won't turn away from my tearful memories
waraiatta kako sae furimukanai
笑いあった過去さえ振り向かない
nor the past where we laughed together
Voice of soul
Voice of you
kanashimi nara kitto tsuyosa ni kawaru hazu
悲しみならきっと 強さに変わるはず
Sadness is sure to turn into strength
I won't cry
I won't fear
I won't stop
takaku tobeba kitto sora no mukou ni todoku
高く翔べばきっと空の向こうに届く
If I jump high enough, I'm sure I'll reach beyond the sky
Voice of mine
Yeah
Voice of soul
～♪
Preview
What kind of king do you wish to be, your highness?
（王騎）あなたさまは どのような
王を目指しておられます？
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）未来に挑む若き王
戦乱の世を照らす光となれるのか？
The young king that challenges the future...
Can he become the light that shines from the sun of war?!
Qualifications of a King
End
Next time,
次回 “王の資格”